Welcome to the Amazon Business Seller Series, Business Only offers module.
After watching this video, you will understand how to offer products exclusively to Amazon
Business customers using business price.
By making your product a business only offer, only registered Amazon Business customers
will be able to see your business price and purchase your product.
In order to make a product a business only offer, when the product is added to inventory,
standard price must be left blank.
If your product already has standard price, it must be deleted and re-added to inventory,
leaving standard price blank.
To add business price to your offers, search "Business Price" in Seller Central and select
business pricing and quantity discounts.
Scroll to the bottom of the help page and select the business price and quantity file
link to bring up the price and quantity file in Excel.
Once the file populates completely, navigate to the "Price Template" tab.
To add business price to a product, simply enter the SKU for the item to which you want
to add the business price offer.
Then add your business price in the business price column.
Save a version of the file as file type "Text tab delimited" for upload.
In your Seller account, select inventory, then select "Add products via upload".
From the drop-down list, select type of file to upload, choose "Price and quantity file".
Browse to the file you just saved, attach the file, then click the "Upload now" button.
When you see the box with the green check mark, you know the file has been submitted.
Check the "Inventory file upload status" table for your processing report to learn
if the upload was successful and to troubleshoot any errors.
This concludes the business-only offer module of the Amazon Business Seller series.
Thank you for tuning in.